[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "licence_name": "Pokemon",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Charmander Smiley",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "PKM001001",
        "img_front": "/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "licence_name": "Pokemon",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Dragonite Hi!",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "PKM001002",
        "img_front": "/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "licence_name": "Pokemon",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Pidgeotto",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "PKM001003",
        "img_front": "/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp"

    
        
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "licence_name": "Pokemon",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Pikachu Smiley",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "PKM001004",
        "img_front": "/img/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "licence_name": "Pokemon",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Vulpix Fancy",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "PKM001005",
        "img_front": "/img/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/pokemon/vulpix-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "licence_name": "Star Wars",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Baby Yoda Blueball",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "STW001001",
        "img_front": "/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "licence_name": "Star Wars",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Boba Fett Fighter",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "STW001002",
        "img_front": "/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "licence_name": "Star Wars",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Luke Skylwalker & Grogu",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "STW001003",
        "img_front": "/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "licence_name": "Star Wars",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Stormtrooper Lightsaber",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "STW001004",
        "img_front": "/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Harry Potter & Hegwid",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "HPT001001",
        "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/harry-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/harry-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Hermione Ball Dress",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "HPT001002",
        "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Luna Lovegood Lion Mask",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "HPT001003",
        "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp"

    
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "licence_name": "Harry Potter",
        "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
        "product_name": "Snape Patronus",
        "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
        "product_price": 1799.99,
        "dues": 10,
        "product_sku": "HPT001004",
        "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/snape-1.webp",
        "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/snape-box.webp"

    
    }
]

    